(Amy:)I'm sure it's just
'cause I'm dating Sheldon.
(Bert:)Mm, actually, I think Sheldon's
popular because he's dating you.
(Penny:)Now Sheldon's popular?
(Penny:)What is happening?
(Howard:)Maybe we should break for lunch.
(Howard:)What time is it?
(Leonard:)According to the world's worst
cuckoo clock, it's 2:00.
(Sheldon:)My head hurts
(Sheldon:)and I'm more tired than ever.
(Howard:)Why don't you just go home?
(Sheldon:)No, I can do this.
(Sheldon:)I just, I just need
another energy drink.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no.
(Howard:)What?
(Sheldon:)I want another one.
(Leonard:)So?
(Sheldon:)That's a craving.
(Sheldon:)That's a sign of
chemical dependency.
(Leonard:)You only had one.
(Sheldon:)No, I know,
(Sheldon:)but plenty of
things are addictive
(Sheldon:)after a single exposure.
(Sheldon:)I mean, crack cocaine,
nicotine, Pringles.
(Sheldon:)You know once one pops
one just can't stop.